# NADER AWADALA

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER



- +359 87 675 3994
- naderawadala@gmail.com
- Check out my website
- Check out my Github
- Add me on LinkedIn

## SKILLS

- HTML/CSS,/Javascript/Typescript
- Bootstrap
- React.js, Redux.js, Angular
- OOP, SOLID principles
- Java
- Spring Framework
- Hibernate
- MSSQL, MySQL, Oracle
- Git, Docker, Jira

## EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

"St. Cyril and St. Methodius" University of Veliko Tarnovo

2018 - 2022

#### HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Secondary School "Emiliyan Stanev" 2013-2018

## PROFILE

I am a dedicated Full Stack Java Developer with over two years of experience in designing, maintaining and implementing software solutions. I am attentive to details and can intensely focus on complex tasks in order to deliver the highest quality final product.

## EXPERIENCE

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

DXC Technology

Apr 2023 - Present

- Developing Spring-based web applications
- Refactoring and upscaling legacy projects to newer Java versions and bringing them up to date to meet the expectations of modern users.

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

pressrelations

Feb 2022 - Mar 2023

- Developing responsive, cross-browser, and user-friendly web applications with React and closely collaborating with UX/Design department and clients to improve final product quality.
- Working on innovative software applications that solve diverse and complex challenges in accordance to design guidelines and coding standards and conventions.

#### INTERN SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

clouway

Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

- Closely working with a small team in an office environment and collaborating to develop software related to ERP systems.
- Solidifying good programming practices and integrating them into my regular work ethic.
- Learning how to work with Git and Docker as well as being introduced and accustomed to the Agile/SCRUM methodology.